♪
- And what's in here?
- 这里面有什么？
[gasps]
[吸气声]
Oh, look.
哦，看。
A tiny toy soldier.
一个小小的玩具士兵。
Candy!
糖果！
Pretty marble.
漂亮的小弹珠。
- Pretty marble. Didn't see that coming.
- 漂亮的小弹珠。没想到吧。
- Can't you watch those dumb egg-opening videos
- 你不能在厨房看那些你迷上的开蛋视频吗？
you're obsessed with in the kitchen?
它们叫奇迹蛋，我并不迷恋。我随时都可以停下来。
- They're called Wunder Eggs, and I'm not obsessed.
- 它们叫奇迹蛋，我并没有迷上。
I can stop anytime I want.
我想停随时都能停。
- Three balloons.
- 三个气球。
- Can that time be now?
- 那现在可以吗？
- It could be.
- 可以的。
- A tiny dinosaur.
- 一只小恐龙。
- But it won't be.
- 但不会是现在。
- Dawn, can you tell Ricky how weird he is?
- 晨，你能告诉里基他有多奇怪吗？
- I've got this, Dawn. Ricky, you're weird.
- 我来处理，晨。里基，你很奇怪。
- Nicky, you know you're not supposed to use Mom's bathrobe when she's out.
- 尼基，你知道妈妈不在时不能用她的浴袍。
You're gonna get us all in trouble.
你会让我们都陷入麻烦的。
Ricky, back me up here. - Dawn's right.
Ricky, 支持我一下。 - Dawn说得对。
- Okay, well, none of us are supposed to be eating junk food.
好吧，我们都不应该吃垃圾食品。
So you're gonna get us in trouble.
所以你会让我们陷入麻烦。
Dicky, back me up here. - Nicky's right.
Dicky, 支持我一下。 - Nicky说得对。
- Well, Mom told you, you can't play any more video games today.
妈妈告诉过你，今天不能再玩电子游戏了。
Dawn, back me up here. - Look, I'd love to,
Dawn, 支持我一下。 - 看，我很想，
but I'm already backing up Dicky from yesterday
但我已经在昨天支持了Dicky
when he backed me up.
当时他支持了我。
- But you owe me a back-up.
但你欠我一个支持。
Nicky, back me up here.
Nicky, 帮我一下。
- Sorry, can't.
对不起，不行。
Part of my back-up with Dawn yesterday
昨天我和Dawn的协议里有一条
was that I can't back you up today.
就是今天我不能帮你。
- What? - Hold on, back up.
什么？
- Are you asking me to back you up?
等等，你在让我帮你吗？
- No, I'm telling you to back up.
不，我在告诉你停下来。
For someone who just took a bath, you stink.
刚洗完澡的人，你闻起来真臭。
- That's lavender.
那是薰衣草的味道。
- Well, it's disgusting.
好吧，那很恶心。
Guys, back me up. - both: It's true.
伙计们，支持我。 - 两个人：这是真的。
- You can't back him up! You both owe me back-ups. - No, we don't. - You owe me a back-up.
- 你不能支持他！你们俩都欠我支持。 - 不，我们没有。 - 你欠我支持。
[overlapping shouting]
[重叠的喊叫]
- Why would I want to back you up?
- 我为什么要支持你？
- Seriously?
- 真的吗？
We can't leave you guys for two minutes.
我们不能离开你们两分钟。
- We just went to the Hickmans' to borrow an egg.
- 我们刚去希克曼家借了个鸡蛋。
- Ooh. - My egg.
- 哦。 - 我的鸡蛋。
- And we come back, and you guys are arguing.
- 我们回来时，你们就在争吵。
You know, I thought we agreed we were gonna have a more harmonious household.
你知道吗，我以为我们同意要有一个更和谐的家庭。
- What? - We did?
- 什么？ - 我们真的同意了？
- We never agreed to that. - It was two minutes ago
- 我们从未同意过那个。 - 那是在两分钟前
when we left for the Hickmans'!
我们离开去Hickmans家的时候！
Tom, back me up on this.
Tom，在这件事上支持我。
- I can't back you up. I owe the kids a back-up
- 我不能支持你。我欠孩子们一次支持
from that time I scratched your car backing up.
从那次我倒车时刮了你的车开始。
- What, you scratched my car? - No, I didn't.
- 什么，你刮了我的车？ - 不，我没有。
Kids, back me up here. - No, he didn't.
孩子们，在这里支持我。 - 不，他没有。
- He's an excellent driver.
- 他是个出色的司机。
- The bumper always looked like that.
- 保险杠一直看起来那样。
- Hey, where'd my egg go?
嘿，我的蛋呢？
- Sorry, I--
对不起，我——
I had to see what was inside.
我得看看里面是什么。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
[whistling]
[吹口哨]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
[cheerful music]
[欢快的音乐]
- I wonder what this family meeting is about.
- 不知道这次家庭会议是关于什么的。
- I don't know, maybe it's to tell you to chew gum louder!
- 不清楚，也许是让你嚼口香糖时声音再大点！
- Oh, I'm sorry. I couldn't hear you
- 哦，抱歉。我听不见你说话
over your clickity-clackity over there.
因为你那边的咔嗒咔嗒声太大了。
Why do you even have a pen?
你为什么还带着笔？
- The cover the sound of his toe cracking.
- 为了掩盖他脚趾的咔嚓声。
- I'm only doing that to cover the sound of his nose whistle.
- 我这么做只是为了掩盖他鼻子的哨声。
- It's seasonal! You can survive until fall.
- 那是季节性的！你可以撑到秋天。
- Kids, your mother and I have noticed
- 孩子们，你们的妈妈和我注意到
you've been acting worse than...usual.
你们最近的行为比平时更糟糕。
- What gave you that idea?
- 你为什么这么想？
- Just a hunch.
- 只是一种直觉。
- Release.
- 释放。
Look, it's obvious that you guys are a little more stressed out
看，很明显你们因为作业和家务变得比平时更紧张，
because of homework and chores,
但你们不能把这种情绪发泄在彼此身上。
but you can't take it out on each other.
所以我们想，如果我们能减轻这种压力，
- So we were thinking that if we could just
那么你们之间的争吵就会减少，
alleviate that stress, then you guys would fight less
从而营造一个更和谐的家庭环境。
and create a more harmonious household.
这就是为什么我们给你们买了这个。
- Which is why we got you this.
- 这就是我们给你们买这个的原因。
Your Own Computerized Optimizer.
你的专属电脑优化器。
all: YOCO!
全体: YOCO！
- This is amazing. - So you know what it is?
- 这太棒了。 - 你知道它是什么吗？
- Of course we know what YOCO is.
- 当然知道YOCO是什么。
- Yeah, she can play music and turn on lights for you.
- 是的，她可以为你播放音乐和开灯。
- Look stuff up for you online.
- 在网上为你查找资料。
- Read me books so Ricky doesn't have to.
- 给我读书，这样Ricky就不必了。
- Plus, she's a learning robot.
- 而且，她是一个学习型机器人。
The more she listens, the smarter she gets.
她听得越多，就越聪明。
- Exactly, and we've synced her up with every room in the house.
- 没错，我们已经将她与房子里的每个房间同步了。
- Check it out, she can even turn on the dishwasher.
- 看这个，她甚至可以启动洗碗机。
YOCO, turn on the dishwasher.
YOCO，启动洗碗机。
- Dishwasher on.
洗碗机已启动。
all: Ooh.
哇。
- Cool, now I'll never have to learn
- 酷，我再也不用学习
how to run the dishwasher. - It's two buttons!
如何操作洗碗机了。 - 就两个按钮！
- Don't tell me which two. I don't want to know.
- 别告诉我哪两个。我不想知道。
- Okay, kids, enjoy YOCO.
- 好了，孩子们，好好享受YOCO。
Your father and I have to go to the store to do some inventory,
你们的爸爸和我得去商店盘点，
so you're on your own.
所以你们自己照顾自己。
- We are? - Really?
- 我们真的要走吗？ - 真的吗？
- Yeah, we trust you.
- 是的，我们相信你们。
- You do? - Us?
- 你们真的相信我们吗？ - 我们？
- Yes, you know the rules.
- 是的，你们知道规矩。
No more video game or tablet usage.
不许再玩电子游戏或使用平板电脑。
No junk food. No using my bathroom.
不许吃垃圾食品。不许用我的浴室。
- What about-- - Or a bathrobe.
- 那其他呢？ - 或者穿浴袍。
And no fighting.
不许打架。
- Anne, are you sure we should trust the kids?
- 安妮，你确定我们应该相信孩子们吗？
- Absolutely not.
- 绝对不应该。
The only reason I bought YOCO
唯一买YOCO的原因
was so that we can monitor the kids while we're gone.
是为了我们不在家时能监控孩子们。
- Oh, you're not gonna monitor me, are you?
- 哦，你不会监控我，对吧？
- I don't know. Do you need to be monitored?
- 我不知道。你需要被监控吗？
- No.
- 不。
Yes.
是的。
- Let's go.
- 我们走吧。
- Did they really just leave us alone?
- 他们真的把我们单独留在这里了？
- Worst parenting move ever.
- 有史以来最糟糕的父母决策。
- Wait.
- 等等。
Before we all go off to do
在我们各自去做
everything they said we shouldn't do,
他们说我们不该做的事情之前，
is there any chance this could be a trap?
有没有可能这是个陷阱？
all: Nah.
不会的。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- YOCO, stream today's Wunder Egg video on my tablet.
- YOCO，在我的平板上播放今天的Wunder Egg视频。
- Streaming now.
- 正在播放。
- Ooh, what's in here?
- 哦，这里面是什么？
Malted milk ball.
麦芽牛奶球。
Fish hook.
鱼钩。
- YOCO, turn up the TV.
YOCO，调高电视音量。
[video game sound effects]
[电子游戏音效]
- YOCO, mute TV.
YOCO，静音电视。
- YOCO, unmute TV.
YOCO，取消电视静音。
- YOCO, mute TV.
YOCO，静音电视。
- YOCO, unmute TV. - YOCO, mute TV.
YOCO，取消电视静音。 YOCO，静音电视。
- Chocolate.
巧克力。
Marshmallow.
棉花糖。
Whipped cream.
鲜奶油。
And caramel.
还有焦糖。
What? It's not junk food.
什么？这不是垃圾食品。
I'm gonna put fruit on it.
我要在上面放水果。
Strawberry...
草莓...
ice cream.
冰淇淋。
- Mute TV! - Unmute TV!
- 静音电视！ - 取消静音电视！
- YOCO, why is it so hot in here?
- YOCO，这里为什么这么热？
All my ice cream is melting.
我的所有冰淇淋都在融化。
- Nicky Harper turned house temperature
Nicky Harper把室内温度调到了95度。
to 95 degrees.
调到了华氏95度。
- That's insane.
太疯狂了。
YOCO, turn house temperature down to 70 degrees.
YOCO，把室内温度调到70度。
- YOCO, 95.
YOCO，95度。
- YOCO, 70.
YOCO，70度。
- Why would you want it to be 95 degrees?
为什么你要把它调到95度？
- 'Cause I didn't want it to be cold
因为我不想洗澡出来后感觉冷。
when I got out of the bath.
尼克，妈妈告诉过你不要用她的浴室，
- Nicky, Mom told you not to use her bathroom,
而且你最好不要用完她所有的昂贵洗发水。
and you better not be using up all her expensive shampoo.
嘿，放松点，又不是……哎哟！YOCO。
- Hey, relax, it's not like...
嘿，放松，又不是...
Ow! YOCO.
哎哟！YOCO。
...I finished the shampoo.
...我把洗发水用完了。
- Finished the shampoo. Ordering more.
用完了洗发水。再订购一些。
- Wait, what just happened?
等等，刚刚发生了什么？
- I think Nicky just made YOCO order more shampoo.
我觉得Nicky刚刚让YOCO订购了更多洗发水。
- Ordering more shampoo.
订购更多洗发水。
- Great, now you just made YOCO order two shampoos.
太好了，现在你让YOCO订购了两瓶洗发水。
- Ordering two shampoos.
订购两瓶洗发水。
- Great, now you just made YOCO order four shampoos.
太好了，现在你让YOCO订购了四瓶洗发水。
- Ordering four shampoos.
正在订购四瓶洗发水。
- Guys, stop, nobody say, "YOCO, order more shampoo,"
伙计们，停下，没人再说，“YOCO，订购更多洗发水”，
because every time you say, "YOCO, order more shampoo,"
因为每次你说，“YOCO，订购更多洗发水”，
she orders more shampoo, and if we keep saying it,
她就会订购更多洗发水，如果我们继续这么说，
we're accidentally gonna make YOCO order 50 shampoos.
我们无意中会让YOCO订购50瓶洗发水。
- Ordering 50 shampoos.
正在订购50瓶洗发水。
all: Nooooo!
不！
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- 91, 92... [phone chimes]
91, 92... [手机提示音]
- 93. - Oh, YOCO alert.
93. - 哦，YOCO提示。
- Oh, ladder! - Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
- 哦，梯子！ - 对不起，对不起，对不起，对不起。
I'll check it after you finish counting these.
我会在你数完这些之后检查。
- One, two... [phone chimes]
- 一，二... [手机铃声]
three, four,
三，四，
five, six...
五，六...
Oh! My phone!
哦！我的手机！
- Whoa!
- 哇！
Ladder!
梯子！
- Okay, okay, okay.
- 好的，好的，好的。
- Anne, Anne, do you really need to think about this?
- 安妮，安妮，你真的需要考虑这个吗？
- Okay. - No, no, that's a $500 phone!
- 好的。 - 不，不，那可是500美元的手机！
You save that phone! - Thank you!
你得救那手机！ - 谢谢你！
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- Is there anything in there about unordering shampoo?
- 里面有关于取消订购洗发水的信息吗？
- No. - Then we should probably
- 没有。 - 那我们可能应该
have YOCO order, like, 50 conditioners.
让YOCO订购，比如说，50瓶护发素。
- Ordering, like, 50 conditioners.
订购，比如说，50瓶护发素。
all: Dicky!
大家：迪基！
- Look, when all this stuff shows up,
- 看，当这些东西都送到时，
Mom and Dad are gonna know that you guys ordered it.
妈妈和爸爸会知道是你们订购的。
- Us?
- 我们？
You ordered some, too.
你也订了一些。
- No, I didn't. - Yeah, you did.
- 不，我没有。 - 不，你有。
Guys, back me up here. - I can't.
伙计们，支持我一下。 - 我不能。
I'm all backed up on back-ups. - Me too.
我已经背书背得满满的了。 - 我也是。
- Fine, YOCO, back me up here.
- 好吧，YOCO，支持我一下。
- No need.
- 不需要。
I back up everything.
我支持一切。
- What do you mean by, you back up everything?
- 你说的支持一切是什么意思？
- I logged every activity that happened this evening.
- 我记录了今晚发生的每项活动。
- YOCO, report activities for the last four hours.
YOCO，报告过去四小时的活动情况。
- Tablet usage, 217 minutes.
平板使用时间，217分钟。
- This is a very bad report.
这份报告非常糟糕。
- Well, at least she has no idea
好吧，至少她不知道
what I was doing in the kitchen.
我在厨房里做了什么。
- Actually, it says here that YOCO can record audio
实际上，这里写着YOCO可以录音
up to 40 feet.
最远可达40英尺。
- Dawn Harper said...
Dawn Harper说...
- Chocolate.
巧克力。
Marshmallow.
棉花糖。
Whipped cream.
鲜奶油。
And caramel.
焦糖。
What? It's not junk food.
什么？这不是垃圾食品。
Where is her mouth?
她的嘴在哪里？
...strawberry.
草莓。
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ 哦，哦，哦，哦，哦 ♪
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- There's gotta be something in that manual
那本手册里一定有什么东西能帮我们摆脱这个困境。
that can help us get out of this mess.
我们开始吧。
- Here we go.
我们只需要重置她。
All we have to do is reset her.
It'll wipe her entire report of the night.
这样会清除她整晚的报告记录。
- Okay. - Great. YOCO, reset yourself.
好的。太好了。YOCO，重置你自己。
- I cannot do that without a password.
没有密码我无法执行这个操作。
- [sighs] - Uh...
叹气。呃...
Oh, hopefully Dad set the password.
哦，希望爸爸设置了密码。
He uses the same one for everything.
他用同样的密码做所有事情。
- Okay.
好的。
all: Tomsgetpasswordy.
大家都说：Tomsgetpasswordy。
- Password correct. - Yes
密码正确。是的
- Nice! - System reset.
- 太好了！ - 系统重置。
- Now we can replace her report with boring stuff
- 现在我们可以用无聊的东西替换她的报告
that'll trick Mom and Dad.
- 这样就能骗过爸爸妈妈了。
- Dicky, she heard that.
- 迪基，她听到了。
- YOCO, reset again. Password, Tomsgetpasswordy.
- YOCO，再次重置。密码，Tomsgetpasswordy。
- System reset.
- 系统重置。
- Okay, now we can replace--
- 好的，现在我们可以替换--
all: Dicky!
- 迪基！
- I just don't think--
- 我只是觉得--
- Anne, I think we're in the wrong house.
- 安妮，我想我们进错房子了。
- Why, Father, is it so hard to believe
为什么，父亲，就这么难以相信
that your children could be getting along?
你的孩子们能和睦相处呢？
- "Why Father"?
为什么，父亲？
- Why, Mother, do I detect a doubting tone?
为什么，母亲，我感觉到一丝怀疑的语气？
- Uh, why, Son, you do.
呃，为什么，儿子，你的确有。
YOCO, read me the nightly report.
YOCO，给我读一下晚间报告。
- Video game and tablet usage, zero.
视频游戏和平板电脑使用，零。
12 algebra equations checked.
12道代数方程已检查。
One hour of Spanish translated.
一小时西班牙语翻译。
Two questions asked.
提出了两个问题。
"What is the Louisiana Purchase?"
"什么是路易斯安那购地？"
And, "How far can a llama spit?"
"还有，"羊驼能吐多远？"
- What? I wanted to know.
- 什么？我只是想知道。
- So what's the answer?
- 那答案是什么？
- Well, back in 1803, the United States--
- 嗯，回到1803年，美国——
- No, no, no, the important one.
- 不，不，不，重要的是那个。
- Ten to fifteen feet with pinpoint accuracy.
- 十到十五英尺，精准无比。
- Impressive.
- 令人印象深刻。
Wow, looks like YOCO really does create a harmonious household.
哇，看来YOCO真的能营造一个和谐的家庭环境。
- It also looks like we'll be able to leave you guys alone again tomorrow night while we finish inventory.
- 看起来我们明天晚上又可以放心让你们独自在家，而我们去完成库存了。
Look, I am really proud of you guys.
看，我真的很为你们骄傲。
Great job.
干得好。
- This is awesome. Our plan is going perfectly.
这太棒了。我们的计划进行得非常顺利。
[doorbell chimes] Oh, I'll get it.
[门铃响] 哦，我去开。
- I've got 50 bottles of shampoo.
我有50瓶洗发水。
- Bushes!
灌木丛！
- What about the, like, 50 bottles of conditioner?
那50瓶护发素呢？
- Bush-es.
灌木丛。
- Who was that?
那是谁？
- The Bushes.
灌木一家。
They just moved in next door and wanted to say hi.
他们刚搬到隔壁，想来打个招呼。
Nice family. - Well, we should say hi back.
好人家。 - 那我们应该回个招呼。
- No, no, no, no, no. They've been moving all day.
- 不，不，不，不，不。他们搬了一整天。
They're really tired.
他们真的很累。
- Oh, well, I guess the Bushes are bushed.
- 哦，那我想布什一家真是累坏了。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Good one, Dad. Still got it.
- 说得好，爸爸。还是那么幽默。
- Well, I guess there's no beating around the Bushes.
- 好吧，我想我们没必要绕弯子了。
Lost it.
没词了。
- I can't believe we actually got away with it.
- 真不敢相信我们居然就这么逃过了。
[knocking at door]
[敲门声]
- And, uh, where do you want me to put the llama?
- 呃，你想让我把羊驼放在哪里？
[llama grunts]
[羊驼咕哝]
- What? I needed to see for myself.
- 什么？我需要亲眼看看。
[llama spits]
[羊驼吐口水]
Impressive!
真厉害！
[llama grunts]
[羊驼咕哝]
[cheerful music]
[欢快的音乐]
- Okay, we are off to finish inventory.
- 好了，我们要去完成库存盘点了。
- Remember, kids, behave yourselves.
- 记住，孩子们，要守规矩。
YOCO's watching.
YOCO在看着呢。
- Of course. - We're good kids.
- 当然。 - 我们是好孩子。
- You can trust us. - Yokey-dokey.
- 你可以相信我们。 - 好的。
Okay, we have three hours to do whatever we want
好吧，我们有三个小时可以做任何我们想做的事
before we have to rest YOCO.
在我们必须让YOCO休息之前。
Indoor dodgeball.
室内躲避球。
- Lame.
- 无聊。
Indoor dodgeball...
室内躲避球...
on roller skates.
穿着溜冰鞋。
- Lame!
- 无聊！
Indoor dodgeball on roller skates...
室内躲避球在滚轴溜冰鞋上...
with buckets on our heads.
戴着水桶在我们的头上。
Do I hear a "lame"?
我听到有人说“无聊”吗？
[llama grunts]
[羊驼咕哝声]
No, I said "a lame."
不，我说的是“一瘸一拐”。
- Nope. - We're good.
- 不是。 - 我们没事。
- Hold on, we can't play roller skate bucket-head dodgeball
- 等等，我们不能在这里玩滚轴溜冰鞋戴水桶头的躲避球
in here. We'll break stuff.
我们会打坏东西的。
Ricky, back me up here.
Ricky，支持我一下。
- No way! This is the first time
- 不可能！这是第一次
I've ever gotten you all to want to do something
这是我第一次让你们所有人都想做某件事
without getting a "lame."
而没有得到一个“无聊”的评价。
Now if you'll excuse me, there's a pickle bucket
现在请原谅我，车库里有一个写着我的名字的泡菜桶。
in the garage with my name on it.
说真的，我在一个泡菜桶上写上了我的名字。
No seriously, I wrote my name on a pickle bucket.
伙计们，我知道我们可以重置YOCO，
- Guys, I know we can reset YOCO,
但如果我们打碎了什么东西，爸爸妈妈会发现的。
but if we break something Mom and Dad will find out.
那如果我们把所有易碎品都放在安全的地方呢？
- So what if we put all the breakables in a safe place?
那样会让你感觉好些吗？
Would that make you feel better?
是的，会的。
- Yes, it would.
那就应该没问题了。准备装备吧。
- And that should do it. Time to suit up.
- 这样应该就可以了。准备穿上防护装备。
- Hold on.
- 等等。
- Is caution tape really necessary?
- 真的需要警戒带吗？
- Yes.
- 是的。
You can never be too safe.
安全永远不嫌多。
[glass shattering]
[玻璃破碎声]
- Ohh. - Not the--
- 哦。 - 不是那个--
[all groaning]
[所有人呻吟]
- Well, at least we didn't break the--
- 好吧，至少我们没打破那个--
[loud crash] Ooh!
[巨大的撞击声] 哦！
- Well, should we get a round in
好吧，在我们清理这一切之前，
before we clean all this up?
我们应该来一轮吗？
- No!
不！
What are we gonna do about all this stuff?
我们该怎么处理这些东西？
- Uh...
呃...
- YOCO, how fast can we order enough glue to fix all this?
YOCO，我们能多快订购足够的胶水来修复这一切？
[doorbell chimes]
叮咚。
- Whoa.
哇。
- Someone ordered a box of Wunder Eggs?
有人订购了一箱奇迹蛋吗？
Maybe there's glue in one of the eggs?
也许其中一个蛋里有胶水？
Slowly, slowly.
慢慢来。
Enjoy it.
享受它。
- Aren't you gonna help us?
你不打算帮我们吗？
- No, I just like to watch.
不，我只是喜欢看。
- ♪ Ohh-ohh, hey, ohh-ohh-ohh ♪
♪ 哦-哦，嘿，哦-哦-哦 ♪
- There.
好了。
Everything is glued back together.
一切都粘回去了。
- Good thing Dad had all that model train glue.
还好爸爸有那么多模型火车胶水。
- Now Mom and Dad will never know.
现在爸爸妈妈永远不会知道。
- But she still does.
但她还是知道。
- That's not gonna be a good report.
那不会是一份好的报告。
- There's not going to be a report.
不会有报告的。
YOCO, reset yourself. Password, Tomsgetpasswordy.
YOCO，重置你自己。密码，Tomsgetpasswordy。
- Password incorrect.
密码错误。
all: What?
什么？
- Someone must have reset her password.
一定是有人重置了她的密码。
- YOCO, who reset your password?
YOCO，谁重置了你的密码？
- Anne Harper.
Anne Harper。
- When did Mom reset the password?
妈妈什么时候重置了密码？
- We're good kids. - You can trust us.
我们是好孩子。 - 你可以信任我们。
- Yokey-dokey.
好的。
- We need to reset the password.
我们需要重设密码。
- What?
什么？
- 'Cause there is a llama in out bougainvillea.
因为有一只美洲驼在我们的九重葛里。
[llama spits] Oh!
哦！
- What are we gonna do now?
我们现在该怎么办？
We can't reset YOCO without the password.
没有密码我们不能重设YOCO。
Oh, she's gonna tell Mom and Dad we--
哦，她会告诉爸爸妈妈我们——
- Shh.
嘘。
She can hear you.
她能听到你说话。
Boy, am I hungry.
天哪，我好饿。
- Me too.
- 我也是。
- Time for a snack. - Whoo-hoo!
- 该吃点零食了。 - 哇呼！
- All right! - Yeah, food!
- 太好了！ - 对，食物！
- Yummy food. - Yes.
- 美味的食物。 - 是的。
- Ha ha! Ha ha!
- 哈哈！哈哈！
Okay, emergency Quaddle.
好吧，紧急情况下的Quaddle。
- What, we're not eating?
- 什么，我们不吃饭吗？
- Okay, this is not good.
- 好吧，这不太妙。
When Mom and Dad come home and ask YOCO for a report,
当爸爸妈妈回家并让YOCO报告时，
we're gonna be so busted.
我们会完蛋的。
- Yeah, that little nerd box knows too much.
- 是啊，那个小书呆子盒子知道的太多了。
- Which means it's either us or her.
- 这意味着不是我们就是她。
- We've gotta get rid of YOCO.
- 我们得摆脱YOCO。
- Get rid of YOCO.
- 摆脱YOCO。
[all scream]
[所有人尖叫]
Ahhh. Ahhh. Ahhh. Ahhh.
啊啊。啊啊。啊啊。啊啊。
- She's mocking us.
- 她在模仿我们。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
♪
- Okay, everybody calm down. She's just a robot.
好的，大家冷静。她只是个机器人。
- A robot that can learn. - But still, it's not like
一个能学习的机器人。
you-know-who is smart enough to know
但毕竟，它不像你-知道-谁那样聪明到知道
that we are trying to you-know-what.
我们在尝试你-知道-什么。
- Danger detected.
检测到危险。
Entering safe mode.
进入安全模式。
Oh, look over there.
哦，看那边。
- She knows we're trying to you-know-what! - Get her!
她知道我们在尝试你-知道-什么！
- [yells]
抓住她！
- Oh.
哦。
- I've got her, I've got her!
- 我抓到她了，我抓到她了！
I don't got her.
我没抓到她。
- I got her!
- 我抓到她了！
Okay, here's what we're gonna do.
好的，我们接下来要这么做。
First, we get rid of YOCO, and then one of us
首先，我们处理掉YOCO，然后我们中的一个人
will buy a new one at the store in the morning.
明天早上到店里去买个新的。
- But then what are we gonna do
- 但之后我们怎么办
when Mom and Dad come home tonight
当爸爸妈妈今晚回家
and see there's no YOCO?
发现YOCO不见了？
- I have got a plan for that, too.
- 我也为此准备了一个计划。
- I don't believe this, guess how much a new YOCO is.
- 我不敢相信，猜猜一个新的YOCO要多少钱。
- $500? - Way too high. It's a smart home device.
- 500美元？ - 太高了。这是一个智能家居设备。
- $50. - Way too low.
- 50美元。 - 太低了。
It's a smart home device.
这是一个智能家居设备。
- 200. - Warmer.
- 200美元。 - 接近了。
- 300. - Colder.
- 300美元。 - 更远了。
- I am 250.
我猜250美元。
- That wasn't colder. They're both off by 50.
- 那不算更远。你们都差了50美元。
So they should be the same temperature.
所以它们应该是同样的温度。
- I get to say what the temperature is. - Okay, guys, focus.
- 我来决定温度是多少。 - 好了，大家，集中注意力。
Mom and Dad are gonna be home soon.
爸爸妈妈很快就回家了。
So we need to get rid of YOCO now.
所以我们现在得处理掉YOCO。
- That's easy.
- 很简单。
Safe mode this.
进入安全模式。
YOCO, turn the dishwasher on.
YOCO，打开洗碗机。
- No.
- 不。
- I command you. Turn the dishwasher on.
- 我命令你，打开洗碗机。
- No. - On.
- 不。
- No. - Fine, I'll do it myself.
- 好吧，我自己来。
Anybody know how to turn this thing on?
有人知道怎么打开这个东西吗？
- I got this.
我来搞定。
Power on.
开机。
- Power off.
关机。
- Power on. - Power off.
开机。
关机。
- Power...off.
开机。
- Nice try. - Dang it!
关机。
We need a new plan.
好，那我自己来。
- Power on.
开启。
- I sure hope YOCO doesn't come outside
- 我真希望YOCO不会出来
and overhear our next plan to get rid of her.
听到我们下一个除掉她的计划。
- Here she comes.
- 她来了。
- Okay, here's the plan.
- 好的，计划是这样的。
We're gonna do...this.
我们要做...这个。
- Bury her!
- 埋了她！
- Warning, this may harm my system.
- 警告，这可能会损害我的系统。
- That's what you get! - Snitches end up in ditches!
- 这就是你的下场！ - 告密者最终会落入沟渠！
- That should do it. - Perfect.
- 应该可以了。 - 完美。
No one's ever gonna know she's here.
没有人会知道她在这里。
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- What did she say? - Yes.
- 她说什么？ - 是的。
- Why, Father, Mother, you're home.
- 怎么了，父亲，母亲，你们回来了。
- Why does YOCO have a sweater on?
- 为什么YOCO穿了件毛衣？
- She was chilly.
- 她觉得冷。
- Okay, YOCO, give me the nightly report.
- 好的，YOCO，给我汇报一下昨晚的情况。
- The children played quietly,
- 孩子们安静地玩耍，
breaking no rules or items of any kind.
没有违反任何规则或损坏任何物品。
Then Ricky was kind enough to knit me this beautiful cozy.
然后Ricky好心地为我织了这件漂亮的毛衣。
End of report.
报告结束。
- That's what happened.
事情就是这样。
- Something's not right.
有些不对劲。
- Yeah, YOCO sounds an awful lot like Ariana Grande.
是啊，YOCO听起来很像Ariana Grande。
- No, I don't. - Yes, you do.
不，我不觉得。
是的，你确实觉得。
- No, I don't. - Yes...
不，我不觉得。
[gasps] ...you do.
是的，你确实觉得。
- No, I don't.
不，我不觉得。
- [sighs] What's going on here?
这里到底发生了什么？
Where's YOCO?
YOCO在哪儿？
- No idea. - Beats me.
- 不知道。 - 我也不清楚。
- No clue. - Kids.
- 没头绪。 - 孩子们。
- Maybe she ran away. We are pretty annoying.
- 也许她跑掉了。我们确实挺烦人的。
- Or maybe she's right here.
- 或者她就在这儿。
- Yay, Squishy found her.
- 耶，Squishy找到她了。
- YOCO, why are you covered in dirt?
- YOCO，你怎么满身是泥？
- Dicky Harper said...
- Dicky Harper说...
- Snitches end up in ditches!
- 告密者最终会掉进沟里！
- Dicky.
- Dicky。
- It was an accident.
- 那是个意外。
- Nicky Harper said...
- 尼基·哈珀说...
- Bury her!
- 埋了她！
- Okay, YOCO, run a full report.
- 好的，YOCO，运行一份完整报告。
- Activity report.
- 活动报告。
List of items broken.
损坏物品清单。
Vase, statue, picture frame,
花瓶，雕像，相框，
grandma's candlesticks...
奶奶的烛台...
- Where is her mouth?
- 她的嘴在哪里？
- Fighting, lying, breaking things?
- 打架，撒谎，破坏东西？
Fighting about lying about breaking things?
因为撒谎而争吵，因为争吵而打碎东西？
- Using all my choo-choo glue?
- 用掉了我所有的胶水？
- This can't happen again.
- 这种事情不能再发生了。
Every time we leave the house, you guys fight and destroy things.
每次我们离开家，你们就争吵并破坏东西。
- Well, on the plus side, we finally stopped fighting when we had to get rid of YOCO.
- 不过，好在自从我们不得不处理YOCO之后，我们终于停止了争吵。
- Well, this should teach you not to take sides against each other
- 嗯，这应该教会你们不要互相反对
and to all learn to back each other up.
并且要学会互相支持。
- Yeah, and when we leave the house,
- 是的，当我们离开家时，
you guys have got to back us up, too.
你们也得支持我们。
- Exactly, just like whenever your mom leaves the house,
- 没错，就像你妈妈每次离开家时，
I have her back. - Yes.
我支持她。 - 是的。
- Her rules are my rules.
她的规矩就是我的规矩。
- Really?
真的吗？
YOCO, play back what happened after breakfast this morning.
YOCO，回放一下今天早上早餐后发生的事情。
- Tom Harper said...
汤姆·哈珀说...
- Come on, Dawn. Let's have some ice cream.
来吧，道恩。我们去吃冰淇淋。
I know Mom said not until after breakfast,
我知道妈妈说早餐后才能吃，
so let's put some bacon on it.
所以我们加点培根吧。
- Nice, Tom.
不错，汤姆。
Okay, well, at least I always have your dad's back.
好吧，至少我总是支持你爸爸。
- Really?
真的吗？
YOCO, play audio from when I was watching
YOCO，播放我在观看《奇迹蛋视频14》时的音频，从7分22秒开始。
Wunder Egg video 14, seven minutes, 22 seconds in.
Anne Harper说...
- Anne Harper said...
我知道你爸爸说过不要再看 egg 视频了，
- I know your father said no more egg videos,
但是，啊，就再看一个吧。
but, ah, just one more.
她的嘴在哪里？
- Where is her mouth?
嘘。
Shh.
（两人同时）她得走了。
- both: She's got to go.
祝你好运摆脱她。
- Good luck getting rid of her.
她挺顽强的。
She's pretty indestructible.
她相当坚不可摧。
- Pfft, fire up the wood chipper, Anne.
- 哼，启动木屑机吧，安妮。
- Leaving safe mode.
- 离开安全模式。
Entering self-defense mode.
进入自卫模式。
- Self-defense mode? What's that?
- 自卫模式？那是什么？
[electrical surge]
[电流涌动]
- Ahhh! She shocked me!
- 啊！她电到我了！
[electricity surging]
[电流持续涌动]
Oh, she's angry!
哦，她生气了！
[overlapping shouting]
[重叠的喊叫声]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[whistling]
[吹口哨]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪